Did you just say you can 't feed yourself
with white-sand brain death ?
What ?
You said you can 't feed yourself
with white-sand brain death .
What does that mean ? I didn 't say that .
You did . Maybe you were still asleep .
You know what , I asked if you wanted breakfast .
If we should get up and get some breakfast .
But I heard you ...
Why are we here ?
It isn 't helping . You 're so frozen these days
I can 't even tell if you 're sleeping or awake .
Hey , come here .
No . Let 's get breakfast .
No , forget breakfast .
No , no , I don 't want to miss the buffet .
Oh .
Come on . Maybe we can catch the omelet chef .
Ladies and gentlemen , ladies and gentlemen .
May I have your attention for a moment , please ?
As some of you may know ,
we are approaching the rainy season
here in Li Tolqa .
For the locals , this period before the storms come
is known as " Umbramaq , " or " The Summoning . "
It is celebrated with traditional music ,
and feasting , and of course , good company .
So , this morning , I would like to welcome you all
to Umbramaq and to anoint you with the " fet yegga " pigment
in the colors of the coast , because it signifies
that we are all bound by friendship
and we are closing out the season together .
Oh , and if any of you would like to purchase " ekki " masks ,
they are still available at the gift shop .
Thank you ! Thank you .
Thank you . Thank you .
Where are we ?
This was your idea , remember ?
Feeling inspired yet ?
Oh , thank you . You didn 't say you were hungry .
There 's a boat tour
of the Tra-kla Island formations this afternoon .
I was thinking we could go on that ,
and make reservations in town for dinner .
We could try the Chinese place .
I don 't think I 'd survive another dinner in town .
Even the idea of it .
Does anyone think it 's a real town ?
Why would they have a Chinese place ?
Is it okay if I go ? I 'll meet you on the beach .
Yeah , sure .
Okay .
Oh , shit .
What 's going on ?
Someone 's making a statement .
One of the locals , I 'd guess .
What do you think he 's trying to say ?
He 's saying that he wants to put a long knife
right through here .
And after you die , he 'll hang your body
at the airport to scare off the other tourists .
Seems a bit extreme .
The Li Tolqans are a melodramatic people .
I loved your book .
Sorry ?
You 're James Foster . I loved your book .
Sorry , is that gauche ?
- I don 't mean to put you on the spot . - Oh , no .
No ... Thank you . Thank you .
It 's just , um , not a lot of people read my book .
I 'm Gabi Bauer .
- Um , I 'm James Foster . - James Foster .
Alban .
This is James Foster .
Hi , nice to meet you . Alban Bauer .
Alban . Pleasure .
He wrote a book that I love .
The Variable Sheath .
Oh . Oh , yeah , I remember .
I thought it was brilliant .
Yes .
James , do you think I could convince you
to join us for dinner this evening ?
I 've been seeing you around the resort
for a few days now and I would love to get to know you .
We have a reservation tonight at Yangs .
Yeah , it was a good , kind of ...
learning experience , I would say .
All right .
Is there anything else I can get you ?
Um , that 's all , I think .
All right , everyone , please have a great meal .
- Thank you . - And let me know anytime
if I can make your experience even more enjoyable .
Interesting guy .
Yes .
This is what is labeled in the resort guide
as a multicultural dining experience .
Well , it certainly is an experience .
So , Alban , what is it you do for a living ?
Oh , architecture , but I 've mostly retired .
Now I run a journal out of Los Angeles called Glass Pane .
You 're French ?
Mm , oh , no . Swiss first , from Geneva .
Then Paris , then LA .
I 'm from London first , then Paris .
- We met there . - That 's how we met .
Oh .
But I couldn 't get work there , so I made Alban move with me .
And what do you do ?
Well , I 'm an actress , of course .
- Oh , really ? - She 's great .
- For commercials . - Okay .
I have a contract with an LA company .
They 've been grooming me .
I specialize in failing naturally .
What does that mean ? " Failing naturally " ?
Finding a natural-seeming way to fail at any given task .
In each of the commercials that I 'm in ,
I 'm the one who simply can 't go on without the product .
It 's ridiculous for me to not have the product .
Okay .
- Show them . - No .
- No , you should . - Yeah .
Please .
You wanna ... ? Do you wanna see it ?
I wanna see . I wanna see .
Here .
She 's amazing .
I just ... I ... I can 't .
How - - how can I - - It 's impossible .
No one can cut bread with a knife .
- No one . - No .
No one . I need the BunChop .
Yeah .
James , don 't you need the BunChop ?
Yeah , you need it .
Clearly .
And see , each act of failure
is a sort of mental and physical puzzle .
You know , I 've been waiting six years for your second book .
That 's true .
Is it coming out soon ?
We 'll - - we 'll see .
Did I say something wrong ?
- Oh , no , no . It 's just he - - he hasn 't been writing . - No , no .
No . I 'm - - I 'm working on it .
Hm , writer 's block ?
Well , I 'm starting to think it might be the lack of talent .
- No . No . - No .
Don 't say that . Please .
I actually came here looking for inspiration .
To a - - to a resort . It 's quite pathetic .
So , what do you do for money then ?
Do you teach , or ?
- He married rich .
That 's a good one .
Well , it 's good for an artist to have a patron , isn 't it ?
- Yes ... Yeah . - Oh , sure .
I 'm in danger of becoming a charitable organization
at this point .
What 's wrong ?
No , I just ...
I don 't understand why we 're doing this .
We barely know these people .
We spent last night with them .
You know what I mean .
We 're not supposed to leave the resort strip .
It 's a poor country . I know it 's not their fault ,
but they have a high crime rate ,
and the guide says they target foreigners .
Well , maybe a little therapeutic mugging
could fix my back .
Come on .
I 'm sure it 's safe if the Bauers are going .
They come here every year .
You 're just happy you found your fan club .
Well , Em , you knew it had to be somewhere .
All right ? It 's one day .
Let 's mix things up a bit . It 'll be fun .
And then now you have to be especially careful ...
Hi !
- Hi . - Hi .
You made it .
- Yeah . - How are you ?
- Good . - Good . Good .
Are you well ? You slept well ?
- Yeah . - Nice to see you .
This is Mr. Thresh .
He 's been kind enough to rent us his car for the day .
... down there .
Can I help you ?
- Oh , thank you . - Yeah .
Isn 't it beautiful ?
Yes . Fuck off . It 's very , very beautiful .
Baby , you need your umbrella ?
Thanks , darling .
- Come on . - Take the wine .
- Take this ? - Yeah , yeah . Sure . Thank you .
James ...
do you want a buffalo sausage ?
No , if I ate another sausage , I would vomit .
Can you vomit first and then eat one ?
They 're coming out perfectly .
Are you trying to kill me ?
I 'm just fattening you for dinner .
You will be our final course .
Once the oil starts coming out of your eyes ,
I 'll fry you with rosemary ,
and Em can eat your balls like a real marriage .
How do you know I haven 't already ?
Look at him , he 's too disobedient .
- Gab ? - Hm ?
Do you want a buffalo sausage , baby ?
No .
Also disobedient ,
and she doesn 't even have balls for us .
So why this guy , if you don 't mind ?
He has no money . Why him ?
I don 't know .
Mm , I suppose it has to be daddy issues .
Daddy issues ?
Well , my father hates him .
Oh , come on , be serious .
She is serious .
My - - my father runs a publishing house ,
and the one thing that he told me
was to never marry a writer .
Of course .
But my father was also a monster ,
so I married the first broke writer
to spill coffee on me .
- Really ? - Yeah .
Almost done .
I 'm sleeping in the back with Em .
Fuck , I 'm still drunk .
I can drive .
You sure ?
Yeah , I 'm good .
All right , thank you .
Okay .
Come on .
No !
What the fuck was that ?
James ?
Stay in the car .
What did you do ?
Oh , my God !
Fuck , James . Fuck !
I didn 't see him .
I couldn 't see !
We have to call someone .
Call who ?
Call the resort , they 'll call our consulate .
Nobody will find us .
How do you call the police ?
No police . Get back in the car .
We 're not calling the police .
W - - wait .
Do you know anything about jail in Li Tolqa ?
This isn 't a civilized country . It 's brutal and it 's filthy .
We 're not getting picked up for this .
Get back in the car now !
It was an accident .
She 's right . It 's very dangerous for us now .
Oh , my God . James , we can 't .
What do you think 's gonna happen to you ?
You 'll be raped by police tonight
and tomorrow they 'll find your body .
That 's how it works with these animals . I 'm not doing that .
You get back in the car , we drive , you go to bed .
Alban and I will deal with Mr. Thresh
directly in the morning . Now !
Now ! Alban , drive !
Hello ?
- Hey . - Hi , there .
Guys , we seem to be locked out .
And who are you ?
Well , we 're guests at the Pa Qlqa .
We 're staying here but we got lost .
How did you get through the gate ?
Excuse me , sir .
But we were just coming back from the disco ,
and we seem to have found ourselves outside somehow .
We - - we must have gone around . Here , look . My key card .
I 'm sorry , I 'm not sure what happened .
Maybe the fence is drunk tonight .
James , you have your key card ?
Guests are not allowed
beyond the border of the compound .
Yeah , we know .
We 're extremely sorry . It won 't happen again .
Thank you .
You 're okay , yeah ? You 're gonna be okay .
We 'll see you at breakfast .
Yeah . I 'm coming .
I 'm coming !
Mr. James Foster ?
Yeah ?
You 'll have to come with us .
Excuse me . Excuse me , where are we going ?
No , no , no !
James !
We 're together . We 're together !
I 'll go - - I 'll go with her .
Em , I 'll find you ! I 'll find you !
Hello ?
Hello ? Can you let me out of here , please ?
Sorry to keep you waiting .
Where 's my wife ?
Mrs. Foster is fine .
I was speaking with her in the other room ,
just down the hall from here .
A lovely woman .
You must feel very lucky .
Smoke ?
No , thank you .
My name is Detective Iral Thresh .
That surname will sound familiar ,
as you met my uncle Dro Thresh ,
who works at the Pa Qlqa Pearl Princess resort .
I 'm told he rented you his car yesterday morning .
James , I 'm going to ask if that 's true ,
but before you answer , I should explain that my uncle
will be in a great deal of trouble
if he rented you the car , so , for his benefits ,
would you agree to answer that he did not rent it to you ?
What would that change for me ?
Nothing . It 's just something I would appreciate ,
given the situation .
Okay .
Thank you .
Mr. Foster , did a resort worker named Dro Thresh
rent you his car yesterday morning
at the Pa Qlqa Pearl Princess ?
No .
Good .
The Bauer couple , Gabi and Alban ,
have already explained that after stealing a car
from a man named Dro Thresh at the Pa Qlqa Pearl Princess ,
you went on a joyride with your wife up the coast .
There you became intoxicated and hit a farmer
named Myro Myron , killing him instantly .
You fled the accident without contacting the police ,
and Mr. Myron 's body was found by his family
yesterday morning .
Your wife has confirmed this account .
Em - - Em did ?
Mm-hm .
She was quite forthcoming .
Under our federal law in Li Tolqa ,
if you are responsible for the death of a man ,
including in the case of an avoidable accident ,
his eldest son should kill you to preserve the family 's honor .
We do it here in the station , on Level B.
Wha ... ?
What ... What 'd you say ?
In the case that there is no son ,
the state will take on that role .
But luckily , Mr. Myron has two sons ,
ages nine and 13 .
But - - but - - but - - but it 's not ... I 'm sorry .
Please . Please . It - - it - -
James , it is unlikely that we will kill you .
Are you aware of the Revised Process of Doubles Act
for International Visitors and Diplomats ?
Physical doubles .
This is the deal my government offers
to foreign visitors in your situation
as part of our longstanding tourism initiative .
For a significant sum , the state will build a double
to stand in for your execution .
Importantly , and this is key to our diplomatic agreement ,
it will also maintain your memories ,
and so will believe itself to be guilty of your crimes
at the time of death .
Do you , James William Foster , consent to be doubled ,
and to the associated fee ,
for the purposes of satisfying our legal proceedings ?
I 'm sorry . I - - I - - I don 't quite understand .
Would you prefer to be executed ?
Please sign .
No , no , no .
Gown , please .
Inside .
This , please .
Are you all right ?
Em ? Where am I ?
We 're still at the station . You 're recovering .
Does it hurt ?
My head is killing me .
They told me the double turned out correctly .
It 's already finished .
The double ?
The surrogate .
They 're waiting for us downstairs .
Often , it takes a few attempts .
Even the smallest imperfection
is unacceptable to the language of the law .
But this one ...
has turned out the first time .
But how ... ?
It 's horrible .
It looks just like me .
You will both be present for the execution .
Oh , no . I don 't want to see it .
This is non-negotiable .
Oh .
Oh , my god . Oh , my god .
Please ... James .
No . No , no , no .
Please . Don 't . I - - I ...
Please don 't . I didn 't ...
Em , please . Em , please !
Em ! Em !
Em , help me ! Em !
Please help ! Em !
Help me ! Help , Em ! Help !
No ! Em , please !
This is the ashes for you to take .
Consider this a souvenir .
A car is waiting to bring you back to the resort .
Can you fucking help ?
All right , there 's a shuttle to the airport in 15 minutes .
James ? James !
Yeah ? Yeah .
What the fuck .
Where the ... ?
What ?
My passport . I can 't find my passport .
What do you mean ?
I don 't know . I always put it in my carry-on . It 's not here .
What do you mean you can 't find it ?
I ... I don 't know where it is .
James , we have to leave .
Well , I know , I 'm looking but it 's not ,
- I can 't - - I don 't know - - - We have to leave !
We have to leave ! We have to leave !
- Fuck !
If you want to go without me , I 'll understand .
I 'll come home as soon as I can get on a flight .
Em ?
It 's really so disgusting .
What ?
It 's really so disgusting that you could just ...
sit there
and watch it happen .
Like a robot .
What 's wrong with you ?
I 'm gonna go down to the front desk ,
see if they can help .
Okay ?
I 'll be right back .
Yes , I understand .
Thank you . Thank you .
Thank you for your patience , Mr. Foster .
Would you like us to extend your room booking ?
Mr. Foster ?
Sorry . Um , is our room still available ?
Yes , Mr. Foster .
Your room is still available
until we close down at the end of the month .
We have a number of free rooms now
with the rainy season coming up .
Okay . Well , let 's say extend it by another week , to start with .
Uh , will this still be under Em Foster ?
Yes .
Wonderful .
Is there anything else I can help you with today ?
No . Thank you .
Are you leaving us ?
As soon as I can .
That 's a shame .
James , I 'm sorry .
Come have a drink with me and let me explain .
Please .
The first year we came , Alban was working as
a consultant on the construction of a new resort .
The Bot Vre 2 . Do you know it ?
No .
It 's just a few compounds over from here ,
north up the beach .
They were installing an infinity pool ,
one of Alban 's designs .
A little pervy , with a glass bottom
that you could look up into from the bar .
But the plate split and fell off the crane ,
and two workers were killed .
The owner of the Bot Vre put the blame on Alban
and so we were arrested . Penalty of death .
And we made a discovery then that you have now discovered .
A discovery .
Are you upset ? Maybe think of it as a gift .
You said you were looking for inspiration .
There 's something to the experience , isn 't there ?
You come out of it feeling ...
it 's hard to explain but I can see it in your eyes ,
if you know what I mean .
Will you come to our villa tonight ?
There are a few others we 've encountered over the years
who share our little secret .
Oh , James . James , you made it .
You 're completely transformed . You look so beautiful now .
I can see the beauty just pouring right out of you .
Here , quickly .
- Yes . - Quickly .
Yes , that 's correct .
A little bit more . Here . Here . Come .
- Thank you . - Come , come , come , come .
Everyone , everyone .
This is the new friend I was telling you about .
James , this is Charles , Jennifer , Dr. Modan ,
and the beautiful Bex .
Nice to meet you .
Do you know that Bex 's father is a film producer ?
Wow .
Maybe he 'll turn your book into a movie .
So , you 're a writer ?
Sort of .
Sort of ?
What does that mean ?
James wrote a very brilliant book that I love .
Mm .
Okay .
So then , what is this book about ?
Don 't harass the man . He 's just had a very bad day .
It 's quite all right .
I 'm just curious about our new zombie .
You don 't have to be afraid , James .
We are all zombies here .
Well , you 're certainly a flesh-eater .
- Oh , please . - Ladies .
Everyone here is a brother , James .
You don 't understand Li Tolqa yet ,
but they are very generous with discipline ,
especially if they know you can pay .
Very conservative outside the resorts .
Very religious .
They will kill you for drugs , blasphemy , sodomy .
Can you guess which one of us was sodomy ?
Honestly , it 's amazing that anyone
is still alive in this country .
You know , James , I 'm glad you could come tonight .
It 's a great time to have you with us .
Dr. Modan is writing a paper
on the Li Tolqan doubling tradition .
It 's Bob , please .
I was wondering if I could ask you a question
while you 're still fresh , as they say .
Sure .
Do you worry they got the wrong man ?
Oh , God .
Do - - do you think , I mean , looking back on it ,
that they killed the real James ?
That was my biggest fear after my own experience .
Because you wake up in that little room ,
and for all you know , they could 've just swapped you out .
Hard to say what happened while you were asleep .
So , what does it matter ?
You have to let it go . I 've let it go .
How can I ?
I 'll never know if I 'm really myself ,
for as long as I live .
Exactly , so who cares ?
What do you think , James ?
Do you fear you may have just witnessed your own demise ?
I can only hope .
Are you feeling all right ?
Ah , yeah , yeah .
Just , um ... Maybe I had too much to drink .
I don 't think that 's it .
The first day is always difficult .
It 's like a new skin working itself into place .
And in your case , I can see something special happening .
I have this ...
pressure ... in my head ...
It will pass .
James ...
Will you trust me tonight ?
He got it from one of the cleaning staff .
It 's fine . Come .
That was a great shot .
James . James , why don 't you come over here for a moment .
I have a proposition for you .
Don 't worry about this gun .
I hear you have a passport problem .
Is that right ?
That can be a lot of trouble in a place like this .
I tell you what ,
I will talk to my connections in immigration
and see if I can help
if you play a little game with us tonight .
Ooh .
We just have a little plan tonight , James .
Just a bit of fun .
Yes , tell him about the mission .
- The mission ? - Yes .
Early this week , the owner of Bot Vre 2 resort ,
he was awarded a medal for promoting Li Tolqan prosperity .
And there was a ceremony on the beach .
We found out the owner lives in a house
just up the hill .
So , we decided tonight we will go get the medal for ourselves .
Just a little game to play , for fun .
It 's actually rather important to us , James .
I mean , after all , he did have us executed .
At a certain point , if you don 't respond to an insult like that ,
you 're such a coward that you 'll just fall to the ground
and never get up again .
What do you say ?
Or maybe we just off you now
so you don 't give us away .
A perfect likeness .
We found it !
Have you ever fired a gun before ?
It would be so easy .
Not everybody gets this chance .
Hey , what are you kids up to in here ?
Just playing chicken .
Oh . Have you seen what he has in this place ?
James , you 're going to want a drink ,
and you 're going to want a cigar .
You have beautiful taste , sir .
I 'm really starting to like you .
Aaahhhhh !
We need to get him inside , right now .
Yes .
My building is just around the corner .
To the right .
It 's okay , honey !
- I need some towels . - James , what 's going on ?
No , no , no , no !
They really should have water in here .
Charles , do you have any water on you ?
They took my bag , sweetheart .
Why don 't you be a gentleman and give Gabi your seat ?
Because I 'm old .
I went for a colonoscopy last month ,
and it was like looking at a painting by Jackson Polyp .
James , do you know why the doubling tradition
is unique to Li Tolqa ?
I 'm starting to think it 's just their poetic flair .
We 've spent years trying to reproduce the process in the lab
but we 're far too literal .
- We just never taken into account ...
Uh , finally .
... the transcend connection - -
Hi .
We 've been waiting in here for hours .
Do you feel you 've been inconvenienced ?
Well ...
Our country is not a playground for foreign children .
It sometimes seems we have forgotten this .
But maybe not today .
You 've tested the limits of our hospitality .
And today I 'm feeling inspired to make a statement .
What do you say ?
Yes , please .
- Hey , hey , hey ! - Hey !
I can walk .
What 's going on ?
- Go now ! - Okay .
Okay .
Come on .
Where are we ?
Detective , where are we going ?
We 're ready to pay now .
Alban !
Leave her alone !
No !
Get away from me !
- Get away from me ! - James !
No ! Go ! Aah !
James !
Bravo ! Bravo !
Well done , James !
I didn 't think you had it in you !
Beautiful .
Em ?
What 's wrong with you ?
With me ?
I 'm leaving .
I don 't have a passport .
Well then , I guess you get to stay .
They told me I 've already paid .
Is this a dream ?
It would make more sense .
You 've gone wrong around the eyes ,
like one of those crabs at the dump .
Go on , then .
Run back to Daddy .
Wait ...
Em left today .
That may be for the best .
We 've been together ten years .
It 's none of my business
but I don 't really think she suits you .
Men are trained by women like Em
to see themselves as weak .
It can take some work to undo .
It can take some blood .
I don 't know about that .
The rainy season is coming .
Will you walk with me ?
What 's that ?
It 's called the ekki gate .
It 's a traditional Li Tolqan root drug .
I got it from one of the guards .
What does it do ?
It 's a hallucinogen .
Also an aphrodisiac .
Drug use is heavily restricted in the modern state ,
but this is considered to be religious .
I want you to show me how strong you are .
It 's horrible .
You 'll come to like it .
How long does it take for it to work ?
Come on .
Pathetic .
Ooh .
Not so loud .
You know , James ,
I spoke to my son-in-law about your passport .
About what ?
Your new - - your new passport .
He said it 's Thresh who is the problem , the detective .
Thresh is holding you back from leaving .
Probably hoping to bring you in again
and fill up his pretty police piggy bank .
The Li Tolqans only understand one thing .
You need to show him that you 're the dominant in this conflict .
Yeah .
They 're like baboons .
Like baboons , but we think we know
just the thing to help .
Oh , yeah ?
Trigeminal neuralgia , James .
It seems the detective is due for a glycerol injection tonight
at Li Tolqa Brain and Spine .
Hey , James . James .
Why don 't you stand down ?
We 're gonna be fast .
Any trouble ?
There was a police van ...
Almost ran me down .
Oh . They just sold out their boss .
Probably had to get drunk first .
Oh .
Show him your strength , James .
Yeah , I like that . I like that . - Attaboy , James .
Come on . Come on . Come on . Come on .
Oh !
Aaaaahhh !
Whooh !
James .
James , come on . You aren 't really upset , are you ?
It 's just a little joke .
We paid the detective to make another double
just to have a little fun with you .
James , open up .
Maybe I 'll bring the double here and you can both fuck me .
Have you ever tried that ?
Don 't be pathetic tonight , James .
It 's so unattractive .
Hi .
James !
Come out , James !
What are you doing in there , James ? Huh ?
Where do you think you 're going , you little baby ! ?
Jaaaaaaaaames !
Members of the bus !
Give us the coward James Foster , or I will come in shooting !
He is a spineless worm and a bedwetter
and he 'd sell his own mother for horse meat to save himself !
Yeah . Jamesy !
Come on . Come on , little baby .
Come on , James . Come on . Come .
You 're so pathetic , James .
A real sucky baby .
I can always pick out a sucky baby for us .
What a joke .
This whole time , we 've been laughing at you .
You 're just a bit of fun for us on our vacation .
And such a terrible driver !
I can 't believe you ran that guy over , James .
Do you remember that ?
We thought we 'd have to get you into trouble ,
turns out you 're such an idiot you did it yourself .
Faster !
I never read your book .
Did you believe that ?
I 'm a good actress .
It was hard to look you up .
One shitty book six years ago that nobody read .
Bad reviews .
You 're so vain , James ,
to actually believe that we read it .
It 's sort of funny ,
but really more than anything , it 's depressing .
Mm .
I do have a review with me , Jamesy .
Have you read this one ?
" The Variable Sheath : As Bad as Its Title .
Seeming to recognize his own lack of talent ,
newcomer James W. Foster overcompensates with pretension ,
failed posturing that only serves to emphasize
how truly terrible this debut really is .
Sheathis a book that has nothing to say
and lacks the words to say it .
One can 't help but wonder whether its very existence
is owed to Foster 's powerful father-in-law ,
media mogul Edward Servek .
Maurice Tate is an overwritten urologist
whose unconvincing marital struggles therein - - "
Ah . Oh , no . Alban , my wine .
- Oh , Jamesy ! Oh , no . Oh , no .
James . What are you doing ?
James !
No ! No !
No ! No ! No !
Oh , no ! James !
Come on .
James .
Ah !
James !
Help ...
No , don 't - -
Help me , Em .
Em , please help me .
Hello ?
He emerges ! Back from the dead !
Hey . James , here .
Come . It 's okay .
It 's okay . Come forward .
Today we 're going to fix you , James .
I know it 's been hard , but believe me when I say
that we are on a mission of mercy .
It 's time for you to shed that disgusting larval mind of yours
and find out what kind of a creature you really are .
Bring the dog .
Come on .
The dog is here for you to complete your transformation .
Only through blood can you release your past .
Sacrifice the dog , James .
Kill the dog .
Fuck you . Fuck all of you .
Pick up the knife , James .
It 's for your own good .
You pick it up .
Go on .
Go fetch !
Come here . It 's okay .
Yeah .
Mm-hm .
Mm .
Well , I 'll land at ten ,
so I 'll be home around 11 , 11 : 30 .
I 'm so sorry , baby .
Really am .
Yeah .
I miss you .
Okay .
Okay , but , I should probably get going
so I don 't miss the shuttle .
But I 'll see you very soon .
All right ?
I love you . Bye .
Thank you .
Thanks .
There you go .
Oh , Charles , did you remind Stacy
I have a spare key under the planter ?
I spoke to her yesterday .
I swear it 's in one ear
and out the other with that girl .
Gabi , what are you two doing when you go back to LA ?
Oh , well , Alban is going straight back to work ,
aren 't you ?
Oh , yes , unfortunately .
The spring issue of the journal is coming up fast ,
and I 'm behind .
Which means I 'll be eating alone
and rearranging the house again .
Please don 't .
Whenever I 'm bored , I rearrange the house
and it drives Alban crazy .
You don 't .
You and Bex must be related .
I like to repaint the walls as well .
Don 't give her any idea .
Alban , that actually reminds me
that we need to pay Jonas for the work he did on the garage .
I paid him last month .
You did ? He just sent me an invoice before we left .
This is a pre-boarding call
for passengers traveling on flight LT 907 to Los Angeles .
Those passengers requiring assistance boarding ,
those with small children , and passengers flying with us
in business class today , please proceed to Gate C.
That 's us .
James , great to meet you .
Hopefully we 'll see you again next year .
Have a good flight .
You too .
This is the final boarding call
for flight LT 606 to Melbourne .
All remaining passengers proceed to Gate One .
I repeat , this is the final boarding call for flight LT 606 .